First of all, in the simulation attribute, the gravity is adjusted to zero. We will introduce the sewing line type without gravity.
Use a rectangular tool to create a board.
Copy and paste the board to move in the horizontal direction of the 2D window so that the board can move in the horizontal direction of the 3D window.
Use the sewing line tool to sew two boards together.
Use the editor sewing line tool. After selecting the sewing line, we can modify the sewing line type in the attribute editor.
Change the sewing line above to Turned.
After changing the sewing line type to Turned, there will be no way to modify the folding strength and folding angle.
If you use the sewing line type as Custom Angle, you can adjust the folding strength and folding angle of the sewing line.
But when the folding strength is zero, the folding angle will fail.
The simulation board will not be folded.
When the folding strength is zero, the folding angle will work.
When the folding angle is less than 180 degrees, fold outward. When the folding angle is greater than 180 degrees, fold inward.
But when the folding strength is higher, the angle of the folding angle is set according to the direction.
When the folding strength is higher than 180 degrees, the angle of the folding angle is set according to the direction.
The 3D sewing line tool shows the marks and hair line effect of the sewing line in the 3D window.
When the strength is zero, the hair line sticker effect in the sewing line will disappear.
The thickness represents the thickness of the hair line sticker.
The thickness of the hair line sticker is the thickness of the hair line sticker.
Now the version in the 3D window looks like a complete version.
Next, let's introduce the unique feature of TURN.
You can clearly see that there is a clear gap in the middle of the sewing line of TURN.
This is because TURN itself uses a sewing line type for overlapping panels.
And the gap between the two panels is the gap between them.
And the strength and thickness of the 3D sewing line will not work.
Next, let's rotate the panels and sew them together.
First, we will modify the sewing line at the bottom to TURN on the custom angle.
For this, we can observe that the TURN on the custom angle is smoother and the TURN on the custom angle is more even.
And you can see that the TURN on the custom angle is smooth.
And the TURN of TURN on the custom angle becomes relatively flat.
The direction of the hair line of the two pieces of the plate should be unified.
If the fabric is too hard, the difference in the sewing line type will be more obvious and the effect of the folding angle will be more obvious.
Here, the plate is hardened first.
You can notice the obvious difference between Custom Angle and Turn.
Reduce the strength of the 3D sewing line to hide the sewing line hair line.
You can notice the obvious gap between the Turn and the sewing line type.
Another thing to note is
If you use Custom Angle,
the direction of the hair line of the plate also needs to be unified.
If you turn it over and over,
the seam of the edge will be cut off after the model is poured out.
If you want to hide the seam,
Hundred magnitude tang will not be provided.
we can notice that there is an obvious gap.
Because the current version is lined with sewing,
the default sewing line type on the internal line of the frozen version is called Turned,
and cannot be modified to Custom Angle.
In this video, I will show you how to modify the
Turned, Custom Angle, and how to modify the
Turned, Custom Angle.